Finding Aid for the Anthony C. Beilenson Papers LSC.0391
UCLA Library Special Collections
- District Office
  - Welby Way Elementary School invitations (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Includes Card invitations to community meeting at School on August 15, 1992; List of Attendees Names & Addresses; Postal Receipt; Expenses & Invoices
  - Malibu Bluffs Park Follow-Up Letter (Box 43, Folder 8)
    Two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Michael Landon Community Center, including The economy, Health Care Reform, & Campaign Finance Reform; Postal Receipts
  - Malibu Bluffs Park invitations (Box 43, Folder 9)
    Copies of Card invitations to community meeting at Michael Landon Community Center on July 25, 1992; List of Names & Addresses of Attendees; Postal Receipt; Expenses & Invoices
  - Kester Avenue Elementary Follow-Up Letter (Box 43, Folder 10)
    Contains two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Kester Avenue Elementary School Community Disability, including Aftermath of The Gulf War, Energy Strategy, Federal Budget Deficit, & Unmet Domestic Needs
  - Kester Avenue Elementary invitations (Box 43, Folder 11)
    Includes two copies of Card invitations to community meeting at Kester Avenue Elementary School on October 26, 1991; List of Attendees Names & Addresses
  - Questionnaire 1991 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    Includes Beilenson Annual Questionnaire Mailings; Draft copies; Table of Random Digits; Postal Invoice; Fax copy
  - Questionnaire Results December 1991 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    Two copies of 1991 Questionnaire Results Mailer, including Fax transmittals of Federal Budget, Campaign Finance Reform, Abortion Counseling, Dependence on Imported Oil, & Health Care Reform
  - Woodland Hills Elementary Follow-Up Letter (Box 43, Folder 14)
    Contains two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Woodland Hills Elementary School, including Aftermath of The Gulf War, Federal Budget Deficit, Energy Strategy, & Unmet Domestic Needs
  - Woodland Hills Elementary invitations (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Includes two copies of invitations to community meeting at Woodland Hills Elementary School on October 5, 1991; List of Attendees & Addresses; Expenses & Invoices
  - Hart Street Elementary Follow-Up Letter (Box 43, Folder 16)
    Contains two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals at community meeting at Hart Street Elementary School, including Aftermath of The Gulf War, Energy Strategy, Federal Budget Policy, & Unmet Domestic Needs
  - Hart Street Elementary invitations (Box 43, Folder 17)
    Includes two copies of Invitation to community meeting at Hart Street Elementary School on September 21, 1991; Legislative Opinion Form Filled Out by Constituent; Attendees Names & Addresses; Expenses & Invoices
  - Reseda Elementary School Follow-Up Letter (Box 43, Folder 18)
    Contains two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals raised at community meeting at Reseda Elementary School, including Aftermath of The Gulf War, National Energy Policy, Federal Budget Policy, Unmet Domestic Needs
  - Reseda Elementary School invitations (Box 43, Folder 19)
    Includes two copies of Invitation Mailer memos from Aides to include certain Constituents in Invitation Lists; List of Attendees Names & Addresses; Expenses & Invoices
  - Tarzana Elementary School Follow-Up Letter (Box 43, Folder 20)
    Contains two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals raised at community meeting at Tarzana Elementary School, including Aftermath of The Gulf War, National Energy Policy, Federal Budget Deficit, & Unmet Domestic Needs
  - Tarzana Elementary School invitations (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Includes two copies of Invitation to community meeting at Tarzana Elementary School on July 27, 1991; List of Attendees Names & Addresses; Expenses & Invoices
  - Follow-Up Letter Westwood (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Contains two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Community Disability at Westwood Elementary School, including Aftermath of The Gulf War, National Energy Policy, Federal Budget Deficit, Unmet Domestic Needs
  - Report on Health Care September 1990 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    Contains two Mailers re Health Car with articles "Solving Our Nation's Health Care Crisis," "How Does The U.S. Compare with Other Nations?" & "How Troubled Is Our Health Care System?"
  - Follow-Up Letter Calabash (Box 43, Folder 24)
    Contains two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Community Disability at Calabash Street Elementary School, including Federal Budget Deficit & Campaign Finance Reform
  - Follow-Up Letter Welby Way (Box 43, Folder 25)
    Contains two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Community Disability at Welby Way Elementary School, including Federal Budget Deficit & Campaign Finance Reform
  - Follow-Up Letter Reseda (Box 43, Folder 26)
    Contains two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Community Meetings at Canoga Park & Woodland Hills, and Apologizing for Not Being Able to Attend Reseda Disability; Discusses Fax transmittals of Federal Budget Deficit & Campaign Finance Reform; Postal Receipt
  - Special report on The Environment July 1990 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    Contains two copies of Mailer "Special Report: The environment," including Articles, "An Environmental agenda for The 1990s" and "Population: The #1 Threat to The Environment"
  - Calabash St. Elementary School (Box 43, Folder 28)
    Includes two copies of Invitation to community meeting at Calabash Street Elementary School on August 7, 1990; memos from Aides to Notify certain constituents re Town Meetings; Legislative Opinion Form Filled Out by Constituent; Attendees Names & Addresses L
  - Welby Way Elementary School invitations (Box 43, Folder 29)
    Includes two copies of Invitation to community meeting at Welby Way Elementary School on August 4, 1990; List of Attendees Names & Addresses
  - Reseda Elementary School invitations (Box 43, Folder 30)
    Includes two copies of Invitation Mailer for community meeting at Reseda Elementary School on August 4, 1990; Letter of Apology from Beilenson for Not Being Able to Attend Disability; Reply to Letter from Constituent re 4th & 5th Amendments; Expenses & Invoices
  - Follow-Up Letter Tarzana (Box 43, Folder 31)
    Contains two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Community Disability at Tarzana Elementary School, including Federal Budget Deficit & Campaign Finance Reform
  - Follow-Up Letter Kester Avenue (Box 43, Folder 32)
    Contains two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Community Disability at Kester Avenue Elementary School, including Federal Budget Deficit & Campaign Finance Reform
  - Tarzana Elementary School (Box 43, Folder 33)
    Includes two copies of invitations for community meeting at Tarzana Elementary School on July 14, 1990; Expenses & Invoices
  - Kester Ave. Elementary School (Box 43, Folder 34)
    Contains two copies of Invitation to community meeting at Kester Avenue Elementary School on July 14, 1990
  - Follow-Up Letter Beverly Vista (Box 43, Folder 35)
    Contains two copies of Letter Summarizing Issue discussed at Community Disability at Beverly Vista Elementary School, including Federal Budget Deficit & Campaign Finance Reform
  - Follow Up Letter Westwood Elementary (Box 43, Folder 36)
    Contains two copies of letter summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Community Disability at Westwood Elementary School, including Federal Budget Deficit & Health Care
  - Beverly Vista Elementary invitations (Box 43, Folder 37)
    Contains two copies of Invitation to community meeting at Beverly Vista Elementary School on March 24, 1990
  - Invitations to community meetings (Box 43, Folder 38)
    Includes Invitation Mailings to Attend community meetings at Reseda, Tarzana, Webster & Castle Heights Elementary Schools; news releases; May, 1987 Town Hall Schedule; Expenses & Invoices; List of Attendees & Addresses; Draft of Town Hall notes; notes of Proceedings; Messages from Aides re Names of constituents Who Request invitations to Meetings
  - Invitations to community meetings (Box 43, Folder 39)
    Includes invitations to community meetings at Woodland Hills, Westwood, Canoga Park, Castle Heights, West Hollywood, & Kester Avenue Elementary Schools; Expenses & Invoices; Attendees Names & Addresses; notes on Beilenson Remarks; Postal Receipt; List of Supplies & Aides Responsible; two Legislative Opinion Forms, Filled Out
  - Follow Up letters from Meetings (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Contains copies of letters Summarizing Fax transmittals at community meetings at Pomelo Drive, Castle Heights, West Hollywood, Kester Avenue, Tarzana, & Reseda Elementary Schools; Attendees Names & Addresses;Fax Draft of Letter
  - ACB Trip--October 13-16, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    Includes List of Supplies for Aides to Bring to Woodland Hills Elementary Hills Elementary School Community Disability, Rental Receipt, Draft Letter for Fundraiser at Peck Home; Letter from Aide to Beilenson re October Fundraiser
  - 1990 Scheduling & Town Halls (Box 44, Folder 3)
    memos re proposed Town Hall and Breakfast schedule for 1990 and Elementary School Location for Next Town Hall meeting
  - ACB Trip September 22-25, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Contains schedule for Visit to District and Appearances; List of Supplies to be Brought by Aides; List of Zip codes and Numbers
  - ACB Trip January 25-31, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    Includes schedule of Beilenson Appearances in District; announcement of Beilenson Talk before Los Angeles World Affairs Council; January 1989 World Affairs Journal; Handwritten Transcript of Beilenson Talk; notice of Preparation for The San Fernando, Valley Rail Transit Project Environmental Impact report
  - Beilenson Trips to District 88 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    Includes schedule of Appearances for Beilenson in District from Jan-June 1988; Town Hall meeting invitations; Legislative Opinion responses; article reprints; Invoices; "Save The Mountains Park" Press Conference; Beilenson Continental Breakfast Invitation, Order for Labels; List of Aids & Supplies; Press Conference Handwritten Transcript; Cable TV Debate with Marmillion announcement
  - 1995 Town Hall notes (Box 44, Folder 7)
    Typewritten Transcripts of community meetings at Sherman Oaks, Woodland Hills, & Encino; Handwritten Transcripts of Unidentified meeting
  - 1994 Town Hall notes (Box 44, Folder 8)
    Includes Typed Transcript of notes of community meetings at Pomelo Drive, Michael Landon Community Center, Woodlake School, Westlake, Hart & Welby Way Elementary Schools
  - 1993 Town Hall notes (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Typed Transcripts of community meetings at Westlake, Kester Avenue, Sumac, Bay Laurel, Lanai Road, & Acacia Elementary Schools, Woodland Hills Town Hall
  - Community Meetings--1996 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    Includes invitations, Expenses & Invoices, Attendees Names & Addresses, Handwritten Transcript, Checklists & Assignments, Typed Transcripts; Meetings at Riverside, Encino, Serrania, & Reseda Elementary Schools
  - Community Meetings--1995 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    Includes invitations, Assignments & Checklist, Expenses & Invoices, List of Attendees Names & Addresses, Typed Transcripts, Postal Receipt, Number of Households in various Zip codes; Meetings At: Encino, Welby Way, Nestle, Westlake, Willow, Acacia, Serra, Elementary Schools; also Serrania, Chandler & Van Nuys
  - Community Meetings--1994 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Includes Invitation Mailers, two Typed Transcripts, & Follow-Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at community meetings at Wilbur Avenue, Lockhurst Drive, Hart Street, Welby Way, Lanai Road, Chandler, Westlake, University, Manzanita, Willow, Riverside; Drive, Encino, Woodlake Avenue, Canoga Park, & Pomelo Drive Elementary School, and Michael Landon Community Center
  - Community Meetings--1993 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Includes Invitation Mailers, Typed meeting notes, & Follow-Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at community meetings at Acacia, Westlake Hissl, Manzanita, Tarzana, Woodland Hills, Welby Way, Lanai Road, Bay Laurel, Sumac, Kester Avenue, & Maple Elementary; Schools, and Michael Landon Community Center
  - Community Meetings--1992 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Includes Invitation Mailers, Typed notes of Meetings, Follow-Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at community meetings at Reseda, Kester Avenue, Hawthorne Street, Hart Street, Woodlake Avenue, Tarzana, Caste Heights, Welby Way, & Woodland Hills Elementary, School; List of Supplies Needed; Beilenson Biographical Sheet; news releases re Linfin Property, Children of Illegal Immigrants
  - Community Meetings--1991 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    Includes Invitation Mailers, Typed notes of Disability, lists of Supplies, & Follow Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Meetings at Westwood, Kenter Canyon, West Hollywood, Overland Avenue, Reseda, Tarzana, Hart Street, Woodland Hills & Kester Avenue, Elementary Schools; Beilenson schedules
  - Community Meetings--1990 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Includes Invitation mailings, memos re Supplies & Cleaning Up Military Installations, Follow Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at community meetings at Castle Heights, West Hollywood, Westwood, Beverly Vista, Marquez, Tarzana, Kester Avenue, Welby, Reseda & Calabash Elementary School; Letter of Apology from Beilenson for Not Being Able to Attend Reseda Elementary School meeting
  - Community Meetings--1989 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    Includes Invitation Mailers, Newspaper article on Fire, Handwritten drafts and Typed Follow Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at community meetings at Castle Heights, Hawthorne, Westwood, Marquez Avenue Westwood, Reseda, Tarzana, Woodland Hills, Park & Kester Avenue Elementary Schools; List of Supplies Needed; Beilenson schedules
  - 1988 Town Halls (Box 45, Folder 7)
    Includes Follow Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Community Meetings at Reseda, Welby Way, Kenter Canyon, Kester Avenue, Castle Heights, Woodland Hills, Canoga Park, & West Hollywood; Beilenson Letter re Aids; "Special Report: Legislative Outlook
  - 1987 Town Halls (Box 45, Folder 8)
    Includes Follow Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Community Meetings at Tarzana, Pomelo Drive, Shirley Avenue, Overland Avenue, Webster, Warner Avenue, Kester Canyon, West Hollywood & Tarzana Elementary Schools, and Roxbury Park; drafts & Additions; Questionnaire Comments and Tabulation Data on Campaign Finance Reform, SDI, Budget Deficit, Nicaragua, & Persian Gulf
  - Beilenson Mailings--1994 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Includes Invitation Mailers, Typed notes of Meetings, List of Attendees Names & Addresses, reports to Westlake Village, Thousand Oaks; Expenses & Invoices; Special Report: Illegal Immigration; Follow Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Community; Postal Receipts; Earthquake Bulletin Information
  - Beilenson Mailings--1993 (1) (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Includes "Special Report: Health Care;" invitations to community meetings; Follow Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Meetings; Attendees Names & Addresses; Expenses & Invoices; Typed notes of Meetings; Letter from Constituent Who Was Not Told of Disability; Legislative Opinion Form
  - Beilenson Mailings--1993 (2) (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Includes invitations to community meetings; lists of Attendees Names & Addresses; Expenses & Invoices; Follow Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Meetings; Handwritten and Typed notes of meeting
  - Beilenson Mailings--1993 (3) (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Includes invitations to community meetings; Follow Up letters Summarizing Issues discussed at Meetings; lists of Attendees Names & Addresses; Expenses & Invoices; Typed notes of Meetings
  - Beilenson Mailings--1993 (4) (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Includes invitations to community meetings; Follow Up letter summarizing issues discussed at Disability; Beilenson 1993 Questionnaire; "Procedure for Sampling from The Returns of A Constituent Survey;" Expenses & Invoices; Typed notes of Meetings
  - Beilenson Mailings--1992 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Includes Invitation Mailers to community meetings; Names & Addresses of meeting Attendees; Postal Receipts; Expenses & Invoices; Follow Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals raised at Meetings; "Report on The Economy;" Beilenson 1992 Questionnaire; Fax Position on Issue, Fax notes of Van Nuys Town meeting
  - 1993 & 1995 Questionnaire Results (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Includes Data Tabulation, Staff Memo re Results of 1995 Questionnaire, Fax of Results, Thoughts, Comments & Draft 1995 Questionnaire, Table of Random Digits, "Procedure for Sampling from The Returns of A Constituent Survey," Tabulation of 1993, Questionnaire
  - 1995 Questionnaire Results (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Newsletter Style Mailer includes constituents' Answers to Questions re Federal Spending, Environmental Protection, Assault Weapons, immigration, School Prayer, Business Subsidies, & Abortion
  - 1995 newsletters Questionnaire (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Newspaper Style Mailing contains Questions for constituents re Federal Spending, Environmental Protection, Assault Weapons, immigration, School Prayer, Business Subsidies, & Abortion
  - 1994 Immigration newsletter (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Newsletter entitled "Special Report: Illegal Immigration;" includes "It's Time to Stop Illegal Immigration" & "Congressman Beilenson's Legislation to Halt Illegal Immigration;" Fax of newsletter
  - 1994 Earthquake newsletter (Box 47, Folder 7)
    Newsletter response to Northridge Earthquake from Beilenson, "Earthquake Information Bulletin;" includes "How to Apply for Federal Disaster Assistance," "Some Types of Assistance for which You Might Qualify," & "Need Help Cutting Through Red Tape?" Updated Emergency Information Bulletin, March 1994, on Four Legal Sheets; newsletter Detailing Federal Action re Earthquake
  - 1993 Questionnaire & Results (Box 47, Folder 8)
    Includes three newsletters "1993 Questionnaire;" "1993 Questionnaire Results and report on The Budget;" & "Reforming Our Health Care System"
  - 1992 newsletters (Health/Econ.) Questionnaire (Box 47, Folder 9)
    Includes Four newsletters: "1992 Questionnaire;" "Report on The Economy;" "Special Report: Health Care (September, 1990);" & "Reports on The economy, Health Care Reform, and The United States' Role in A Changing World"
  - 1991 Questionnaire & Results (Box 47, Folder 10)
    Contains two Mailings: "1991 Questionnaire" & "1991 Questionnaire Results;" Questions Asked Re: Federal budget, Campaign Finance Reform, Abortion Counseling, Dependence on Imported Oil, Health Care Reform
  - 1990 Environment newsletter (Box 47, Folder 11)
    Contains two copies of July, 1990 newsletter, "Special Report: The environment," including articles, "An Environmental agenda for The 1990s" & "Population: The "1 Threat to The Environment"
  - 1989 Questionnaire, Questionnaire Results, & Budget Deficit Newsletter (Box 47, Folder 12)
    Contains Four newsletters: "1988 Questionnaire Results," 1989 Questionnaire," "1989 Questionnaire Results," & "Special Report: The Federal Budget Deficit"
  - Questionnaire Tabulations (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Includes materials re Questionnaires, including Fax of 1991 Results; 1989 Questionnaire Mailing, Rough Draft, Data Tabulation; 1988 Questionnaire & Results, Data Tabulation; 1986 Questionnaire Results, Data Tabulation; 1984 Questionnaire, Poll Result; Data Tabulation; 1983 Questionnaire, Results & Data Tabulation; 1982 Questionnaire, Results & Data Tabulation; Fax 1992 Results
  - Questionnaires, newsletters, Town meeting Letters, Misc. Mailing (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Includes Mailing from 1978-1989, Re: Federal Budget Deficit, Expanding Health Care Protection, report on Aids, Slowing The Arms Race, Nicaragua, Reforming The Tax Code, Special Interest Influence in Congress, Tax Reform, Social Security, Environment; Defense, Reaganomics, Santa Monica Mountains, Flood Insurance, Energy Saving, SALT II; Questionnaires & Campaign flyers
  - ABC newsletter--Crime, Federal Deficit, Illegal Immigration 9/94 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    Two copies of newsletter, "Good News on three Major Issues: crime, The Federal Deficit, and Illegal Immigration;" articles include, "Fighting Crime with More Police, More Punishment, and More Prevention," Cutting The Federal Deficit and Revitalizing, economy," "Curbing Illegal immigration," & A Brief Update on Five Other Key Issues"
  - 1994 Community Town Hall Meetings (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Includes invitations to community meetings and Follow Up letters Summarizing Fax transmittals discussed at Meetings; Attendees Names & Addresses; Expenses & Invoices; Meetings at Woodlake Avenue, Canoga Park, Chandler, Pomelo Drive, Encino, Manzanita, Riverside Drive, Wilbur Avenue Elementary Schools and Michael Landon Community Center; notes on Riverside Drive Town meeting
  - UCLA (Box 51, Folder 3)
    Correspondence with UCLA Special Collections; Directions to Campus
  - EIS/EIR for Arts Park LA (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Draft report re Environmental Impact Statement (EIS)/Environmental Impact report (EIR) for Arts Park LA prepared for Department of The Army Los Angeles District Corps of Engineers and City of Los Angeles Department of Recreation and Parks
  - Flood Protection Project (Box 73, Folder 2)
    Draft Environmental Assessment report entitled "Tillman Water Reclamation Plant Flood Protection Project" prepared for The U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Los Angeles District
  - Drainage Area Review (Box 73, Folder 3)
    Final Feasibility report entitled "Los Angeles County Drainage Area Review"
  - W.H. Conference. on Small Business (Box 74, Folder 6)
    Report, newsletters, newspaper clippings, correspondence, brochures, Misc. Information re White House Conference on Small Business, major Fax transmittals include Small Business Implementation Network, Small Business Concerns
  - W.H. Conference. on Small Business (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Report, newsletters, newspaper clippings, correspondence, brochures, misc. information re White House Conference on Small Business, major Fax transmittals include Public Law 101- 409 which provides for each senator, representative, and governor to appoint one delegate and one, alternative to The National Conference, Minority Delegates' Caucus
  - W.H. Conference. on Small Business (3) (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Report, newsletters, newspaper clippings, correspondence, brochures, Misc. Information re White House Conference on Small Business, major Fax transmittals include Appointing Delegates, Small Business Development Centers
  - W.H. Conference. on Small Business (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Report, newsletters, newspaper clippings, correspondence, brochures, Misc. Information re White House Conference on Small Business, major Fax transmittals include State Information, Mission Statement of Achieving Economic Growth Through Innovation, Navix, Inc.
  - Arts (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Handbook, newsletters, newspaper clippings, correspondence, brochures, Misc. Information re Arts, major Fax transmittals include Artistic Discovery, Guide to The National Endowment for The Arts, Dance
  - ACB Office Procedures, views (Box 76, Folder 4)
    Newsletters, correspondence, Information Sheet re Beilenson Office Procedures, views, major Fax transmittals includes His views on Health Care, immigration, California economy, Federal Deficit, etc.
  - ACB Office Procedures, views (2) (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Van Nuys Airport--Part 150 Study Steering Committee Proceedings (1) (Box 76, Folder 6)
    Agenda, minutes, report re Van Nuys Airport, Part 150 Study, major Fax transmittals include Noise Compatibility Program, Noise Control